[{"No": 0, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "8074"}, {"No": 1, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "7559"}, {"No": 2, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "1948"}, {"No": 3, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "6069"}, {"No": 4, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 5", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "9026"}, {"No": 5, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 6", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "5711"}, {"No": 6, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 7", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "6848"}, {"No": 7, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 8", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "9509"}, {"No": 8, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 9", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "8067"}, {"No": 9, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 10", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "1385"}, {"No": 10, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 11", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "5209"}, {"No": 11, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 12", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "7684"}, {"No": 12, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 13", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "3047"}, {"No": 13, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 14", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "7144"}, {"No": 14, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 15", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "3602"}, {"No": 15, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 16", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "1316"}, {"No": 16, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 17", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "1599"}, {"No": 17, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 18", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "9620"}, {"No": 18, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 19", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "8570"}, {"No": 19, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 20", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "1744"}, {"No": 20, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 21", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "5627"}, {"No": 21, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 22", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "6761"}, {"No": 22, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 23", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "9277"}, {"No": 23, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 24", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "5798"}, {"No": 24, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 25", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "4238"}, {"No": 25, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 26", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "0419"}, {"No": 26, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 27", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "1142"}, {"No": 27, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 28", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "7596"}, {"No": 28, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 29", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "0399"}, {"No": 29, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 30", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "6159"}, {"No": 30, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 31", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "8831"}, {"No": 31, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 32", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "0332"}, {"No": 32, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 33", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "7503"}, {"No": 33, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 34", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "7459"}, {"No": 34, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 35", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "7248"}, {"No": 35, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 36", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "6735"}, {"No": 36, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 37", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "4956"}, {"No": 37, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 38", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "0299"}, {"No": 38, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 39", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "5820"}, {"No": 39, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 40", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "8885"}, {"No": 40, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 41", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "8135"}, {"No": 41, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 42", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "2291"}, {"No": 42, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 43", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "0883"}, {"No": 43, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 44", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "2255"}, {"No": 44, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 45", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "3878"}, {"No": 45, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 46", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "3639"}, {"No": 46, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 47", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "9362"}, {"No": 47, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 48", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "4679"}, {"No": 48, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 49", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "7098"}, {"No": 49, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 50", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "5472"}, {"No": 50, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 51", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "9903"}, {"No": 51, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 52", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "8911"}, {"No": 52, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 53", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "0171"}, {"No": 53, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 54", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "3025"}, {"No": 54, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 55", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "4197"}, {"No": 55, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 56", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "8815"}, {"No": 56, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 57", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "6190"}, {"No": 57, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 58", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "0818"}, {"No": 58, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 59", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "1083"}, {"No": 59, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 60", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "9622"}, {"No": 60, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 61", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "2103"}, {"No": 61, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 62", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "0266"}, {"No": 62, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 63", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "5436"}, {"No": 63, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 64", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "1137"}, {"No": 64, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 65", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "1641"}, {"No": 65, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 66", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "5179"}, {"No": 66, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 67", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "3998"}, {"No": 67, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 68", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "7617"}, {"No": 68, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 69", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "5767"}, {"No": 69, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 70", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "7504"}, {"No": 70, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 71", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "3309"}, {"No": 71, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 72", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "9290"}, {"No": 72, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 73", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "4219"}, {"No": 73, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 74", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "9975"}, {"No": 74, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 75", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "3583"}, {"No": 75, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 76", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "2348"}, {"No": 76, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 77", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "8983"}, {"No": 77, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 78", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "3071"}, {"No": 78, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 79", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "2628"}, {"No": 79, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 80", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "7295"}, {"No": 80, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 81", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "1388"}, {"No": 81, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 82", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "1046"}, {"No": 82, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 83", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "4266"}, {"No": 83, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 84", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "1628"}, {"No": 84, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 85", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "4559"}, {"No": 85, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 86", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "8941"}, {"No": 86, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 87", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "1360"}, {"No": 87, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 88", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "4915"}, {"No": 88, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 89", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "7970"}, {"No": 89, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 90", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "0150"}, {"No": 90, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 91", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "0518"}, {"No": 91, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 92", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "8109"}, {"No": 92, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 93", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "0550"}, {"No": 93, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 94", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "2054"}, {"No": 94, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 95", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "1660"}, {"No": 95, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 96", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "8888"}, {"No": 96, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 97", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "4111"}, {"No": 97, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 98", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "0603"}, {"No": 98, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 99", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "6615"}, {"No": 99, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 100", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "7241"}, {"No": 100, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 101", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "6135"}, {"No": 101, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 102", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "9461"}, {"No": 102, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 103", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "5453"}, {"No": 103, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 104", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "4875"}, {"No": 104, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 105", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "2723"}, {"No": 105, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 106", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "3835"}, {"No": 106, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 107", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "7682"}, {"No": 107, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 108", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "7026"}, {"No": 108, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 109", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "7721"}, {"No": 109, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 110", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "7973"}, {"No": 110, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 111", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "2706"}, {"No": 111, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 112", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "6572"}, {"No": 112, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 113", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "0723"}, {"No": 113, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 114", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "3290"}, {"No": 114, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 115", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "4954"}, {"No": 115, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 116", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "0596"}, {"No": 116, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 117", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "1376"}, {"No": 117, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 118", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "5158"}, {"No": 118, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 119", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "7057"}, {"No": 119, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 120", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "9974"}, {"No": 120, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 121", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "4087"}, {"No": 121, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 122", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "8818"}, {"No": 122, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 123", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "7220"}, {"No": 123, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 124", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "7134"}, {"No": 124, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 125", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "9208"}, {"No": 125, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 126", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "8248"}, {"No": 126, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 127", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "6734"}, {"No": 127, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 128", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "6056"}, {"No": 128, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 129", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "9670"}, {"No": 129, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 130", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "6055"}, {"No": 130, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 131", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "9672"}, {"No": 131, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 132", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "6046"}, {"No": 132, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 133", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "8884"}, {"No": 133, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 134", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "3937"}, {"No": 134, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 135", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "7548"}, {"No": 135, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 136", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "5218"}, {"No": 136, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 137", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "8547"}, {"No": 137, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 138", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "2178"}, {"No": 138, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 139", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "7381"}, {"No": 139, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 140", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "9493"}, {"No": 140, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 141", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "1663"}, {"No": 141, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 142", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "6544"}, {"No": 142, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 143", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "1366"}, {"No": 143, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 144", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "0935"}, {"No": 144, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 145", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "9078"}, {"No": 145, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 146", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "2640"}, {"No": 146, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 147", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "2791"}, {"No": 147, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 148", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "1414"}, {"No": 148, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 149", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "3727"}, {"No": 149, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 150", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "8599"}, {"No": 150, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 151", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "4618"}, {"No": 151, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 152", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "9393"}, {"No": 152, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 153", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "6380"}, {"No": 153, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 154", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "1399"}, {"No": 154, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 155", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "8218"}, {"No": 155, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 156", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "1131"}, {"No": 156, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 157", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "8800"}, {"No": 157, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 158", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "0867"}, {"No": 158, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 159", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "7789"}, {"No": 159, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 160", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "1347"}, {"No": 160, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 161", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "0621"}, {"No": 161, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 162", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "3017"}, {"No": 162, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 163", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "2024"}, {"No": 163, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 164", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "8619"}, {"No": 164, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 165", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "1350"}, {"No": 165, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 166", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "2163"}, {"No": 166, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 167", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "3327"}, {"No": 167, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 168", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "7562"}, {"No": 168, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 169", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "7409"}, {"No": 169, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 170", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "4354"}, {"No": 170, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 171", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "6479"}, {"No": 171, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 172", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "6725"}, {"No": 172, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 173", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "4989"}, {"No": 173, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 174", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "4287"}, {"No": 174, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 175", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "2232"}, {"No": 175, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 176", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "9807"}, {"No": 176, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 177", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "9769"}, {"No": 177, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 178", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "3384"}, {"No": 178, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 179", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "1098"}, {"No": 179, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 180", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "4379"}, {"No": 180, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 181", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "9928"}, {"No": 181, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 182", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "4147"}, {"No": 182, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 183", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "0284"}, {"No": 183, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 184", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "3905"}, {"No": 184, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 185", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "6895"}, {"No": 185, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 186", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "8751"}, {"No": 186, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 187", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "2980"}, {"No": 187, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 188", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "0459"}, {"No": 188, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 189", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "0492"}, {"No": 189, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 190", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "9707"}, {"No": 190, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 191", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "2746"}, {"No": 191, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 192", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "8480"}, {"No": 192, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 193", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "0927"}, {"No": 193, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 194", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "4717"}, {"No": 194, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 195", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "5550"}, {"No": 195, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 196", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "8892"}, {"No": 196, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 197", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "4570"}, {"No": 197, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 198", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "8381"}, {"No": 198, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 199", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "1677"}, {"No": 199, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 200", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "7308"}, {"No": 200, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 201", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "3627"}, {"No": 201, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 202", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "2872"}, {"No": 202, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 203", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "6187"}, {"No": 203, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 204", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "7856"}, {"No": 204, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 205", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "5574"}, {"No": 205, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 206", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "0511"}, {"No": 206, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 207", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "6730"}, {"No": 207, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 208", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "3337"}, {"No": 208, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 209", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "5621"}, {"No": 209, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 210", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "4520"}, {"No": 210, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 211", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "5462"}, {"No": 211, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 212", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "6327"}, {"No": 212, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 213", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "5384"}, {"No": 213, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 214", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "6229"}, {"No": 214, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 215", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "7017"}, {"No": 215, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 216", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "6700"}, {"No": 216, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 217", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "0557"}, {"No": 217, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 218", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "3942"}, {"No": 218, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 219", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "4178"}, {"No": 219, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 220", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "7042"}, {"No": 220, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 221", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "6965"}, {"No": 221, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 222", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "9906"}, {"No": 222, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 223", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "4946"}, {"No": 223, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 224", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "2091"}, {"No": 224, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 225", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "8249"}, {"No": 225, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 226", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "5121"}, {"No": 226, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 227", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "7108"}, {"No": 227, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 228", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "0614"}, {"No": 228, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 229", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "2944"}, {"No": 229, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 230", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "8097"}, {"No": 230, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 231", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "6370"}, {"No": 231, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 232", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "9188"}, {"No": 232, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 233", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "1152"}, {"No": 233, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 234", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "5001"}, {"No": 234, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 235", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "5632"}, {"No": 235, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 236", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "1896"}, {"No": 236, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 237", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "8237"}, {"No": 237, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 238", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "9835"}, {"No": 238, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 239", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "6942"}, {"No": 239, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 240", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "6839"}, {"No": 240, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 241", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "7542"}, {"No": 241, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 242", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "8029"}, {"No": 242, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 243", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "5211"}, {"No": 243, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 244", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "0513"}, {"No": 244, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 245", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "6066"}, {"No": 245, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 246", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "4481"}, {"No": 246, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 247", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "9705"}, {"No": 247, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 248", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "1029"}, {"No": 248, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 249", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "9364"}, {"No": 249, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 250", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "7084"}, {"No": 250, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 251", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "3908"}, {"No": 251, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 252", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "0407"}, {"No": 252, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 253", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "0126"}, {"No": 253, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 254", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "8919"}, {"No": 254, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 255", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "2949"}, {"No": 255, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 256", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "2920"}, {"No": 256, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 257", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "3663"}, {"No": 257, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 258", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "3596"}, {"No": 258, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 259", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "1616"}, {"No": 259, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 260", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "1084"}, {"No": 260, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 261", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "5233"}, {"No": 261, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 262", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "2711"}, {"No": 262, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 263", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "7860"}, {"No": 263, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 264", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "3157"}, {"No": 264, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 265", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "5840"}, {"No": 265, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 266", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "5677"}, {"No": 266, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 267", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "7829"}, {"No": 267, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 268", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "4146"}, {"No": 268, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 269", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "0667"}, {"No": 269, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 270", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "6680"}, {"No": 270, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 271", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "3904"}, {"No": 271, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 272", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "6729"}, {"No": 272, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 273", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "9554"}, {"No": 273, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 274", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "5789"}, {"No": 274, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 275", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "5059"}, {"No": 275, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 276", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "8725"}, {"No": 276, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 277", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "2301"}, {"No": 277, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 278", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "8324"}, {"No": 278, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 279", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "5532"}, {"No": 279, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 280", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "2298"}, {"No": 280, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 281", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "8781"}, {"No": 281, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 282", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "5347"}, {"No": 282, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 283", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "2698"}, {"No": 283, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 284", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "9627"}, {"No": 284, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 285", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "2925"}, {"No": 285, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 286", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "3087"}, {"No": 286, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 287", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "1293"}, {"No": 287, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 288", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 3, "Password": "4464"}, {"No": 288, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 289", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "2732"}, {"No": 289, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 290", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "9192"}, {"No": 290, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 291", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "0183"}, {"No": 291, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 292", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 2, "Password": "4330"}, {"No": 292, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 293", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "3472"}, {"No": 293, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 294", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "9482"}, {"No": 294, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 295", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 1, "Password": "9685"}, {"No": 295, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 296", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "5651"}, {"No": 296, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 297", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "0018"}, {"No": 297, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 298", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "4428"}, {"No": 298, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 299", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "9556"}, {"No": 299, "Question": "\u0e04\u0e33\u0e16\u0e32\u0e21\u0e02\u0e49\u0e2d\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 300", "Options": ["\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 1", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 2", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 3", "\u0e15\u0e31\u0e27\u0e40\u0e25\u0e37\u0e2d\u0e01\u0e17\u0e35\u0e48 4"], "Correct": 4, "Password": "9580"}]